I keep thinking in my head that we all need a mom.
I've been thinking that we really all need a tremendous hug in the world right now.
But in our country, we need you to be Mamala of the country.
Do you like it?
Yeah, I'll be talking about that and a number of other weird, cringy, ridiculous things
while I'm on my unlikable tour.
I'll be in Baltimore, Maryland next weekend at the Baltimore Comedy Factory.
Go to AmandaSeals.com to get your tickets.
I'll be in Boston the week after that and then Rally the week after that.
We got a lot to talk about, y'all.
And you know me, I'm doing much more than just comedy.
Let's sell these shows out.
See you there.